NGUYEN VAN DUNG

Java Developer

| Ha Noi, Viet Nam

SUMMARY

I'm a software engineer, have been working with Java for 2 years. I'm passionate researching and resolving complex problem related to data and analytics, willing learn and adapt with new technologies. I looking forward to work in high velocity dynamic environment.

EXPERIENCE

September 2018 – Present Foss Development & Services Joint Stock Company

Ha Noi, Viet Nam

- Design and implement data collectors & extractors for "Online Public Service System Vietnam Registry", specialized in vehicle registration; allow deep analytics, export and reporting within our organization. Maintain stability of existing system and ensure extensibility with new, continuous changing requirements over time. Using Java, Elasticsearch, MariaDB, Jasper Report, Liferay Portal for back-end.
- Design and implement category management, manage schedule departure and arrival for ship, payment service for "Business Software Vietnam Maritime Administration". Using Java, MariaDB, Jasper Report, Liferay Portal for backend.
- Design and implement manage recruiment module for "Web Portal Netnam", which manage recruitment news in system. Using Java, Lucence Search, MariaDB, Liferay Portal for back-end.
- Maintain "Database Convert Tool From Oracle To MariaDB" using Spring Boot.
- Fix bugs and implement change requests for a "Work Management Software Mobilink". Using: Java, Spring Boot, MariaDB, Liferay Portal for back-end.

PORTFOLIO

April 2020 - Present

Booking Hotel System

Description: Booking Hotel System is an online short-term rental platform and hospitality service, connecting customers looking to rent a property with the property owners.

Stack: Spring MVC, Elasticsearch, VueJS, MySQL.

Source:

- Back-end: https://github.com/ngvandung/bookingproject
- Front-end: https://github.com/ngvandung/bookingfe

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Proficient using: Java, Tomcat, Git, Webservice, Elasticsearch, SOAP/Restful API, MySQL/MariaDB.
- **Knowing**: Spring Framework, Docker, Hibernate, Servlet, JSP.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2021 Electric Power University

Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Software engineer

APPLY POSITION Junior Java Developer